<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
  <content>
    <title>Unique Videos</title>
    <paragraph>We know all companies are not alike, so,we work with you to create the best solution for your company. Your company offers a solution to your clients, but sometimes that solution or product needs some explaining. </paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Unique Solution</title>
    <paragraph>Your company offers a solution to your clients, but sometimes that solution or product needs some explaining. That's where we come in. We create high impact, exciting VIDEOS that explain your product, service, software or business.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Ignite Intrest</title>
    <paragraph>We use fast-paced, brain stimulated imagery and content to ignite and then build their interest in your solution and ignite their buying habits. Includes Collaborative Scripting, Creative Storyboard and Custom Drawings.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Solution Oriented Videos</title>
    <paragraph>We work with you to create the best video solution for your company. We work with you to explain your solution or product with high impact, exciting videos.  Since all our videos are custom we can focus on the Solution that you provide clients.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Explain Your Process</title>
    <paragraph>Our team of Professionals can explain your product, service or procedure in an Animated Explainer Video! Our Videos powerfully explain things step-by-step, and it keep your viewers' attention!</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Experienced Professionals</title>
    <paragraph>We create custom video content tailored for your business and marketing objectives. Our team of highly experienced videographers, motion designers, graphic designers, illustrators, and copywriters will create a unique, custom video for your business.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Custom Content</title>
    <paragraph>We don't force you into template or stock images and unlike other companies you're not stuck with one choice of drawing style with us you can choose from many different styles.  We create custom content for you!</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Collaborative Process</title>
    <paragraph>The images used in your video should be customized for your specific business model. We collaborate with you to brainstorm the best custom ideas. We don't force you into template or stock images.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Custom Script</title>
    <paragraph>We don't ask you to fill out a lame generic survey and we don't use freelance writers. We listen to you, ask you lots of questions and listen some more and then when we're on the same page and headed in the right direction we collaborate with you live over Google Docs to create a custom script using powerful words to engage and motivate your viewers to take action. Say no to surveys and companies that won't spend a lot of time to talk to you.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Clear, Compelling Videos</title>
    <paragraph>Many businesses run into a wall because they can’t quickly explain their product or service in a clear, compelling way. When you work with us, we take the time to learn about your business, apply our expertise and knowledge to uncover your story.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Engage Your Audience</title>
    <paragraph>We specialize in communicating technical messages in an engaging way your target audience can understand.  By getting to know you and your product we are able to create a custom video to engage your target audience.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Video Professionals</title>
    <paragraph>Our incredible team of professional strategists, writers, artists and video experts are ready and excited to work with you. We can’t wait to help you accomplish your business goals!</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Target Your Audience</title>
    <paragraph>We focus on explaining your product or service to your target audience in exciting, engaging ways.  That is why we craft your video from the ground up by learning from you about your company.</paragraph>
  </content>
</data>
